geg.ca 2009-02-26

# GEG / Privacy Policy

Welcome to the Gillett Entertainment Group ("GEG") website located at [http://www.GEG.ca](http://www.geg.ca/) (the “Website”). It is the policy of GEG to respect your privacy, and the privacy of all visitors to the Website. This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) has been established to help you understand our commitment to protecting your privacy, and the steps we take to ensure it.

Your privacy is very important to us and we want you to know everything we do and don’t do with the information you provide. Our guiding principle is that any information we collect from you will be treated with the utmost care and respect, and every effort will be made to ensure the information is kept private.

This information is accurate as of its publishing on September 1, 2008. GEG reserves the right, at any time and without prior notice, to modify the Policy. Any changes to the Policy can be found at this URL.

If you have any questions about the Policy, please contact:

GEG Legal Services  
BCF LLP  
1100, boul. René-Lévesque Ouest, 25e étage  
Montréal (Québec) H3B 5C9

or use the Website [contact form](http://www.geg.ca/show/contact_us).

The Policy should be read in conjunction with the [Terms of Use](http://www.geg.ca/show/page/terms_and_conditions), as both documents govern your use of the Website.

**No collection of personal information**  
GEG does not gather any of your personal information while you are surfing this Web site, unless you willingly subscribe to a specific service, such GEG membership, and are asked to provide such information.

**Gathering of information for statistical purposes**  
GEG automatically collects certain information to help us understand how our users use the Website, but none of this information identifies you personally. For example, each time you visit the site we automatically collect your IP address, browser and computer type, access times, the web page from which you came, and the web page(s) you access. We use this information only to better understand your needs and the needs of Website users in the aggregate, and to be able to trace fraudulent activities if necessary. GEG also makes use of information gathered for statistical purposes to keep track of the number of visits to the Website with a view to introducing improvements.

**Non-disclosure of personal information**  
Except as provided in the next paragraph, GEG does not divulge any personal information gathered on its Web site to third parties. Moreover, GEG does not sell its list of Website users. Only the employees, representatives, subcontractors, or officers of GEG are responsible for the management and development of the Website, and only these individuals have access to the information collected there. These employees, representatives, subcontractors, or officers all have been instructed to comply with the Policy.

Notwithstanding anything in the Policy to the contrary, we may share any information we have collected about you or that you have submitted: (1) in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish, protect, or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims or demands; (2) if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person; (3) if we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding situations that involve abuse of the Website infrastructure or the Internet in general (such as voluminous spamming, denial of service attacks, or attempts to compromise the security of the Website infrastructure); (4) to a parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control with GEG (in which case we will require such entities to honour this privacy policy); and (5) if GEG is acquired by or merged with another entity (in which case we will require such entity to assume our obligations under this privacy policy).

**Tracking Technology ("Cookies")**  
GEG may use tracking technology ("cookies") on the Website and by using the Website you agree to their use. Cookies are small text files placed on your hard drive when you visit a web site, in order to track use of the site and to improve the user experience by storing certain data on your computer. The Website may use “session cookies,” which improve your browsing experience by storing certain information from your current visit on your computer. Furthermore, third parties may place advertisements on the Website which use cookies to gather data about users who click on the advertisements, yet none of this data can personally identify you.

Your browser can be set to refuse cookies or delete them after they have been stored. However, please note that deleting these cookies may reduce your user experience on the site by requiring you to re-enter certain information such as login information or language preference.

**Risks associated with the Internet**  
Despite GEG's efforts to ensure third parties will not access or obtain your personal information through the Website, complete confidentiality and security cannot currently be guaranteed on the Internet. Communication via the Internet is subject to interception, loss, or alteration. You acknowledge and agree that GEG cannot be held responsible for damages resulting from the transmission of confidential information or personal information over the Internet and that such communications are at your own risk.

**Hyperlinks to other sites**  
GEG's Web site may contain hyperlinks enabling users to visit sites maintained by other companies. GEG has no control over these sites and is not responsible for those listed on its site. Any information you transmit to these sites will be subject to those sites' applicable privacy policies.

**Limitation of Liability**  
GEG, nor any of its respective officers, directors, owners, officials, partners, partnerships, principals, employees, affiliates and other related entities, servants, agents, representatives, successors and assigns, will not be held liable for any damages resulting from the misuse of any information collected through the Website by any third party, or any misuse of any information collected through the Website not in violation of the Policy.

**Consent**  
By browsing GEG's Web site, you consent, without qualification, to the Policy.
